[

{
"answer": "JavaScript","question":"one of the 3 main languages of the web, it is used to program the behavior of web pages"
},
{
"answer": "id","question":"an HTML attribute that specifies a unique identification name for one HTML element"
},
{
"answer": "script","question":"HTML tag that creates a section for writing Javascript code"
},
{
"answer": "variable","question":"a named storage location that can store changeable information, depending on conditions or on information passed to the program. A number, string, or boolean that can be set, changed, and recalled"
},
{
"answer": "var","question":"a Javascript command that defines a new variable. This is the older version of let"
},
{
"answer": "let","question":"a Javascript command that defines a new variable. This is the newer version of var"
},
{
"answer": "button","question":"a clickable HTML element that should cause something to change"
},
{
"answer": "onclick","question":"an attribute that sets the Javascript that should run when a button is clicked"
},
{
"answer": "getElementById() ","question":"a Javascript command that allows you to change something with a specific ID name"
},
{
"answer": "innerHTML","question":"changes the text within an HTML element"
},
{
"answer": "class","question":"an HTML attribute that specifies one or more classifications for HTML elements. It is usually used to define styles for a group of elements you want to look the same"
},
{
"answer": "alert()","question":"a Javascript command that displays a popup box with a message and an OK button"
},
{
"answer": "prompt()","question":"a Javascript command that displays a popup box that asks the user for input"
},
{
"answer": "function","question":"a named group of programming instructions that performs a specific task. Reusable abstractions that reduce the complexity of writing and maintaining programs."
},
{
"answer": "function definition","question":"the keyword “function” followed by a name, (), and curly brackets that contain lines of Javascript code."
},
{
"answer": "function call","question":"the name of a Javascript function followed by (). This tells the computer to run the lines of code inside the function definition."
},
{
"answer": "console","question":"a debugging section where you can input commands and view error messages and other output messages from the computer"
},
{
"answer": "debugging","question":"the process of finding and removing errors"
},
{
"answer": "syntax","question":"the set of rules that defines a correctly structured document in a language"
},
{
"answer": "comment","question":"notes that can be read in the code but do not affect the code in any way"
},
{
"answer": "mathematical operator","question":"a mathematical character that takes two numbers and performs a calculation on them. For example, +"
},
{
"answer": "assignment operator","question":"the operator used to assign a new value to a variable. In JavaScript, ="
},
{
"answer": "equality operator","question":"returns True if the value on the left is equal to the value on the right, otherwise it returns False. In JavaScript, it is the characters =="
},
{
"answer": "string","question":"a data type that stores a sequence of characters which could include letters, numbers, spaces, symbols and punctuation. For example, \"steve!\", \"can't\", \"$9.99\""
},
{
"answer": "camelCase","question":"process of naming multi-word variables without spaces and so that words in the middle of the phrase begins with a capital letter. For example, numberOfCars, iPhone, eBay"
},
{
"answer": "display","question":"sets how an HTML element is shown on a web page (inline or block, for example) or if it is not shown"
},
{
"answer": "block-level element","question":"starts a new line and takes up the full width of its parent element"
},
{
"answer": "inline element","question":"does not start on a new line and only takes up as much width as necessary"
},
{
"answer": "conditional","question":"also known as selection, a statement that uses a boolean condition to determine whether or not to run other statements. Usually an if-then statement"
},
{
"answer": "transition","question":"a CSS property that controls animation speed when changing CSS properties. Instead of having changes take effect immediately, you can cause the changes to take place over a period of time"
},
{
"answer": "event listener","question":"a Javascript function that waits for an event to occur such as a key press or a mouse click"
}
]
